DALE HOLSTEIN

704.390.8893 DHolstein30@gmail.com github.com/Zarnerz linkedin.com/in/dale-holstein

Passionate and driven web developer proficient with JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Git, Node.js, AJAX, SQL, MongoDB and APIs. Adept analytical problem solver with experience working in a diverse work environment. Life-long learner of new technologies and constantly refining skill set.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Pic-a-Flic

- Movie selection application to help indecisive movie watchers to choose a movie to watch. User can select parameters to filter results and then has three random films returned using multiple API calls.
- Lead JavaScript & API Developer on a team of 4
- https://supernatmor.github.io/PADM/

Bamazon

- Amazon-like storefront using mySQL and Node.js. Includes separate views for Customers, Managers, and Supervisors.
- Sole Developer
- https://github.com/Zarnerz/liri-node-app
- Video Demonstration: https://youtu.be/Pmtoe-WZ3r8

Dragon Ball Giphy API App

- Web application that allows users to input their favorite characters from the Dragon Ball universe to create a button that will display 10 gifs when pushed. Utilizes JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX and the Giphy API to grab the data and then append them onto the page which was made with HTML, CSS, & Bootstrap.
- https://zarnerz.github.io/GiphyAPI-HW6/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Crew Member - Autobell Car Wash - Indian Trail, NC

October 2015 - Present

Substitute Teacher - Boone County Schools - Madison, WV

April 2015 – September 2015

 Facilitated learning and organize learning resources to ensure students are reaching curriculum objectives.

Administrative Assistant - Bluegreen Vacations - St. Augustine, FL May 2014 - December 2014

 Provided excellent customer service, ensured accuracy and confidentiality of information, facilitated coordination between marketing and sales departments

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Charlotte

August 2017 - February 2018

- UNCC Coding Bootcamp Javascript Full Stack Web Development
- An intensive 24-month long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications. Curriculum includes: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, AJAX, APIs, Firebase, Node.js, SQL, MongoDB, Handlebars.js, Express.js, React.js, & Git.

Marshall University

December 2013 Magna Cum Laude

Bachelor of Arts: History